bbcshop.com 2014-04-16

# Security and Privacy at BBC Shop

### 1\. Introduction & General Terms

BBC Worldwide Limited ('BBCW') is committed to protecting your personal information when you are using BBCW services. We want our services to be safe and enjoyable environments for you to use. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide to us. In order to provide you with the full range of BBCW services, we are sometimes required to collect information about you. This privacy policy explains the following: 

  * what information BBCW may collect about you;
  * how BBCW will use information we collect about you;
  * whether BBCW will disclose your details to anyone else;
  * when BBCW may use your details to contact you;
  * your choices regarding the personal information you have provided to us;

As set out above, BBCW is committed to safeguarding your personal information. Whenever you provide such information, we are legally obliged to use your information in line with all laws concerning the protection of personal information, including the Data Protection Act 1998 (these laws are referred to collectively in this Privacy Policy as the "data protection laws"). Our websites may contain hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties. These third party websites have their own privacy policies, including cookies, and we urge you to review them. They will govern the use of personal information which you submit or which is collected by cookies whilst visiting these websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk.

Back to top

### 2\. What Information will BBCW collect from me?

When you sign up to participate in or receive a service from BBCW, such as newsletters, competitions, magazine subscriptions, ordering products, readers' offers, live chats, message boards, surveys or online registration we may ask for personal information about you. This can consist of information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone or mobile number or date of birth. Different services or webpages may ask for different personal information.

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable BBCW and its service providers to provide you with the services you select.

Please note that sometimes on particular services (e.g. chat forums) you may be asked to provide or you may volunteer additional personal information and sometimes sensitive personal information (e.g. your political opinions, religious beliefs, sex life or health).

We may also use your IP address for some of our website services (please see our Cookies policy). 

Back to top

### 3\. How will BBCW use the information they collect about me?

BBCW will use your personal information for a number of purposes including the following:

  * for service administration purposes, which means that BBCW may contact you for reasons related to the service you have signed up for, as set out in section 5: When will BBCW contact me? below (e.g. to provide you with password reminders or to notify you that a particular service has been suspended for maintenance);
  * to notify you of changes to our service;
  * to contact you about a submission you have made to our websites or other publications, including any content you provide (follow the link to our Code of Conduct at the bottom of the main pages of our websites for more details about making online submissions);
  * to personalise or improve the way BBCW content and advertising is presented to you online:
    * BBCW may collect your IP address (an IP address is a number that can uniquely identify a specific computer or other network device on the internet) and place cookies (see our Cookies Policy) for the purpose of improving our sites and enhancing your user experience, sometimes including the display of selected ads which are appropriate to your browsing pattern. This information is not used to develop a personal profile of you;
    * IP addresses may also be used to identify the location of users, the number of visits from different countries and also to block disruptive use;
    * to analyse and improve the services offered by a BBCW website, e.g. to provide you with the most user-friendly navigation experience;
  * to manage our competitions and contact the winners;
  * to meet product orders or requests for services or information; to process payments; and to keep our records up to date;
  * where you have specifically consented to be contacted for these purposes, to send you direct marketing by telephone, post or email about special offers and current or new products that you may be interested in;
  * to enable other people or businesses to carry out work on our behalf; and
  * where you have given us your permission, to pass your information to carefully selected organisations to allow them to tell you about their special offers or products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * Where BBCW proposes using your personal information for any other uses we will ensure that we notify you first. You will also be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use other than as listed above.

Back to top

### 4\. Will BBCW share my personal information with anyone else?

Generally, we will only use your information within the BBC Worldwide Group of companies (including BBC Worldwide Group companies which are situated outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"), such as Lonely Planet, which is based in Australia) in order to provide the service/product you have requested. We will not pass your information to other members of the BBC Worldwide Group for marketing purposes unless you have consented to this.

We will only disclose your data to third party data processors with your consent or where we need to do so in order to provide a service. The data processors to whom we may pass your data will be BBC Worldwide Group companies and appropriately contracted third parties. Otherwise, we will keep your information confidential except where disclosure is required or permitted by law (for example to government bodies and law enforcement agencies) or as described in section 7: Offensive or inappropriate content on BBCW's websites below.

BBCW will require all third party data processors to whom your information is disclosed to comply strictly with its instructions and BBCW will require that they do not use your personal information for their own business purposes.

Where we share your information with BBC Worldwide Group and third party companies which are situated outside the EEA we will ensure they treat your information with the same protection we do.

Back to top

### 5\. When will BBCW contact me?

BBCW may contact you:

  * in relation to the functioning of any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that BBCW can deliver the services to you;
  * in relation to any contribution you have made to any BBCW website, message board or other service;
  * where you have opted to receive newsletters or other correspondence;
  * to invite you to participate in surveys about BBCW services (participation is always voluntary);
  * to carry out obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and BBCW; and
  * for marketing purposes where you have specifically agreed to this (see section 6: Will I be contacted for marketing purposes? below).

Our websites and other publications will give you detailed information about how BBCW will contact you in relation to specific services.

Back to top

### 6\. Will I be contacted for marketing purposes?

BBCW won't contact you for marketing purposes, or promote new services to you unless you agree to be contacted for these purposes.

Back to top

### 7\. Offensive or inappropriate content on BBCW's websites

If you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on a BBCW website, or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour, BBCW may use your personal information to stop such behaviour.

Where BBCW reasonably believes that you are or may be in breach of the law (e.g. because content you have posted may be defamatory), BBCW may use your personal information to inform relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider or law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour.

Back to top

### 8\. What if I am a user aged 16 or under?

If you are aged under 16, please get your parent/guardian's permission before you provide personal information to BBCW. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

Back to top

### 9\. How long will BBCW keep my personal information?

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant service, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with BBCW or BBCW's corporate retention schedule. If you wish to cancel your registration with any of BBCW's websites, you may do so by following the "unsubscribe" instructions on the relevant website. If you change your profile to opt-out of receiving communications, your record may stay on the system so we can ensure that we do not contact you in the future.

Where you contribute to a BBCW service or website, BBCW will generally only keep your content for as long as is reasonably required for the purpose(s) for which it was submitted.

Back to top

### 10\. Can I find out what personal information BBCW holds about me?

Under the Data Protection Act you have the right to request a copy of the personal information BBCW holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. (We may charge £10 for information requests and will require you to prove your identity with 2 pieces of approved photographic identification.) We will use reasonable efforts to supply, correct or delete personal information about you on our files.

If you have any requests or questions about this or any other question about this Privacy Policy please see section 12: Contacting BBCW about this Privacy Policy at the bottom of this document or contact [dataprotection@bbc.com.](mailto:dataprotection@bbc.com)

Back to top

### 11\. Changes to BBCW's Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may be updated from time to time so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information to any BBCW service. The date of the most recent revisions will appear at the bottom of this page.

Back to top

### 12\. Contacting BBCW about this Privacy Policy

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please contact:

Head of Data Protection  
MC2 A6  
BBC Worldwide Limited  
Media Centre  
201 Wood Lane  
London  
W12 7TQ  
United Kingdom

Email: [dataprotection@bbc.com](mailto:dataprotection@bbc.com)

Last updated: May 2012

Back to top

BBC Worldwide is committed to protecting your personal information when you are using BBCW services. We strive to make our services safe and enjoyable environments for you to use. We have created this separate cookies policy in order to provide comprehensive information about BBC Worldwide’s use of cookies across its website portfolio.

Back to top

### 2\. Information about Cookies

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to here as a "device") browser from a website's server and is stored on your device's hard drive. Each website or third party service provider used by the website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website or third party service provider to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites or other third party service providers. A cookie will contain some anonymous information such as a unique identifier and the site name and some digits and numbers. It allows a website to remember things like your preferences or what’s in your shopping basket.

**What is a browser?**

A browser is an application that allows you to surf the internet. The most common browsers are Chrome, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Safari. Most browsers are secure and offer quick and easy ways to delete information like cookies. Please see the section below Updating Your Settings.

**What do cookies do?**

Cookies record information about your online preferences and allow us to tailor the websites to your interests. Information supplied by cookies can help us to analyse your use of our sites and help us to provide you with a better user experience. For example, you may choose to personalise the content of a website in order to see the latest news and weather for your region. In order to do this, a cookie is placed on your device to remember where you live so that we deliver the information that has been requested by you. This is a prime example of how cookies are used to improve your experience of a website.

**Change your Browser Settings’**

You can choose how cookies are handled by your device via your browser settings. The most popular browsers allow users to a) accept all cookies, b) to notify you when a cookie is issued, or c) to not receive cookies at any time. If you choose not to receive cookies at any time, the website may not function properly and certain services will not be provided, spoiling your experience of the website. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

Back to top

**First Party Cookies**

First party cookies are set by the website you are visiting and they can only be read by that site.

**Third Party Cookies**

Third party cookies are set by other organisations that we use for different services. For example, BBC Worldwide uses external analytics services and these suppliers may set cookies on BBC Worldwide’s behalf in order to report what’s popular and what’s not. The website you are visiting may also contain content embedded from, for example, YouTube or Flickr and these sites may set their own cookies.

**Session Cookies**

Session Cookies are stored only for the duration of your visit to a website and these are deleted from your device when your browsing session ends.

**Persistent Cookies**

This type of cookie is saved on your device for a fixed period. Persistent cookies are used where we need to know who you are for more than one usage session. For example, if you have asked us to remember preferences like your location or your username.

**Flash cookies**

Many websites use Adobe Flash Player to deliver video and game content to their users. Adobe utilise their own cookies, which are not manageable through your browser settings but are used by the Flash Player for similar purposes, such as storing preferences or tracking users.

Flash Cookies work in a different way to web browser cookies; rather than having individual cookies for particular jobs, a website is restricted to storing all data in one cookie. You can control how much data, if any, may be stored in that cookie but you cannot choose what type of information is allowed to be stored. You can manage which websites can store information in Flash cookies on your device via the website storage settings panel on the Adobe website.

**Web beacons, clear GIFs, page tags and web bugs**

These are all terms used to describe a particular form of technology implemented by many websites in order to help them to analyse how their site is being used and, in turn, to improve your experience of their site. They may also be used to target any advertising being served on the web page you are viewing.

A web beacon (or similar) usually takes the form of a small, transparent image, which is embedded in a web page or an email. They are used in conjunction with cookies and send information such as your IP address, when you viewed the page or email, from what device and your (broad) location.

Back to top

### 4\. How do we use Cookies?

Cookies enable us to identify your device, or you when you have logged in. We use cookies that are strictly necessary to enable you to move around the site or to provide certain basic features. We use cookies to enhance the functionality of the website by storing your preferences, for example. We also use cookies to help us to improve the performance of our website to provide you with a better user experience.

Typically, we use cookies to deliver the following services throughout the pages of our websites:

  * To enable us to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information repeatedly;
  * To recognise that you may have requested that we remember your username and password so you don't need to enter your details each time you visit the site;
  * To ensure that if you are purchasing a product or service via our websites, your experience is smooth and secure;
  * To record what people like and don’t like on the website and the popularity of various elements of the website so that we can ensure that it works properly at points of high usage. BBCW also uses a number of independent measurement, advertising and research companies. They gather information regarding the visitors to BBCW sites on our behalf using cookies, log file data and code which is embedded on our website. BBCW uses this type of information to help improve the services it provides to its users.

Back to top

### 5\. Analytics on our Websites

Coremetrics and Google Analytics provide anonymised statistical information for us. They process IP addresses and information from cookies used on our sites so we know how many page views we have, how many users we have, what browsers they are using (so we can target our resources in the right way to maximise compatibility for the majority of our users) and, in some cases, in which country, city or region they are located.

Back to top

### 6\. Updating your settings

If you would like to opt out of Analytics cookies, please do so by clicking on the links below:

Back to top

On a quarterly basis, we conduct an audit of all cookies being used across the website portfolio.

Back to top

Please contact the [Data Protection](mailto:dataprotection@bbc.com) team at BBC Worldwide if you would like more information on the cookies that we use and their purposes.

Policy Last Updated: May 2012

Back to top

### 1\. Credit/Debit Card Security 

Shopping at BBC Shop is safe and guaranteed. All the information that you enter is private and secure. The BBC places great importance on maintaining the security of the information that you provide and for this reason we use advanced Internet security system to safeguard your data. All the data that you send through, including your name and address, is encrypted and converted into code before it is transmitted across the Internet. Therefore in the extremely unlikely event that the data should be intercepted, it would be encrypted and difficult to decipher. 

The BBC Shop also checks the authenticity of the credit card details when they are entered. 

In the event of unauthorised use of your credit card or debit card most banks and credit card companies either cover the charges that result or may limit your liability to £50. 

Do not send credit/debit card details via standard email, as this is not secure, please use the online shop or telephone us to place your order. In the unlikely event of unauthorised card use please be sure to contact your card issuer immediately as per your contractual arrangement with them. 

Back to top

### 2\. How safe are my details when I place an order? 

BBC Shop places great importance on maintaining the security of the information that you provide and for this reason we use advanced Internet security systems to safeguard your data. In addition, BBC Shop.com is protected by a GeoTrust Certificate ensuring all data you send through, including your credit/debit card number, name and address, is encrypted and converted into code before it is securely transmitted over the internet. Therefore in the extremely unlikely event that the data should be intercepted, it would be encrypted and difficult to decipher. 

Back to top

### 1\. Introduction to Terms & Conditions

This page (together with the documents referred to on it) sets out the terms and conditions on which we supply the goods and services listed on our website at www.bbcshop.com (BBC Shop). Please read these terms and conditions carefully before ordering any goods or services from BBC Shop. You should understand that by ordering any of our goods or services, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions.

Each time you make a purchase from BBC Shop, you will need to indicate your acceptance of these terms by clicking on the button marked "I Accept" during the checkout process. Please understand that if you refuse to accept these terms and conditions, you will not be able to order any goods or services from our site.

The terms and conditions are subject to change at any time, and it is your responsibility to check these terms and conditions regularly before ordering goods in case there are any changes. 

Back to top

BBC Shop is a division of BBC Worldwide Limited (BBCW, We, Us), a wholly owned subsidiary of the BBC. BBC Shop is operated under licence by BBCW a company incorporated in England and Wales under company number 1420028, whose registered office is at Media Centre, 201 Wood Lane, Media Centre, London, W12 7TQ. Our VAT number is 333289454. 

Back to top

If you have any questions regarding BBC Shop, its goods, services or an order that you have placed, please contact us by: (a) emailing us at [bbcshop@bbc.com](mailto:bbcshop@bbc.com); (b) completing the feedback form available [**here**](https://www.bbcshop.com/scat/contactus); (c) calling us on 0844 846 1417 (Monday - Friday 08:30-18:00 - all UK calls will be charged at national rates). 

Back to top

### 4\. Service & Product Availability

Our site is only intended for use by people resident in the [**Serviced Countries.**](https://www.bbcshop.com/scat/deliveryinformation#wherewedeliverto) We do not accept orders from individuals outside of those countries. Please review our Serviced Countries page before ordering any goods/services from us. There may also be restrictions on certain products for certain international delivery destinations (for example, DVD’s), so please review the information on that page carefully before ordering the products. 

Goods dispatched by BBC Shop to addresses outside of the European Union are generally not subject to VAT.

If you order goods for delivery outside the UK, they may be subject to import duties and taxes which are levied when the delivery reaches the specified destination. You will be responsible for payment of any such import duties and taxes. Please note that we have no control over these charges and cannot predict their amount. Please contact your local customs office for further information before placing your order. 

Please also note that you must comply with all applicable laws and regulations of the country for which the products are destined. We will not be liable for any breach by you of any such laws. 

Delivery times are clearly displayed on the site next to each individual item. If no delivery date is specified, your order will be fulfilled within 30 days of the date of the Dispatch Confirmation, unless there are exceptional circumstances.

If BBCW has insufficient stock to deliver the goods you have ordered, BBCW will not charge your credit card until the date your order is sent to you. BBCW will inform you by e-mail at the address given in your order form and any sum which may have been credited from your credit card will be re-credited to you no later than 30 days after the date of your order. 

Back to top

By placing an order through our site, you warrant (promise) that: 

  * (a) you are legally capable of entering into binding contracts; 
  * (b) you are at least 18 years old; and 
  * (c) the information given on your order form is complete and accurate. 
  * (d) you will keep your password confidential and will be responsible for all of your account activity. If you think that anyone else might have obtained your password, you must change it immediately. 

As a consumer, you have legal rights in relation to products that are faulty or not as described. Advice about your legal rights is available from your local Citizens Advice Bureau or Trading Standards office. Nothing in these Terms will affect these legal rights. 

Back to top

All orders are subject to acceptance by us and availability of the requested item(s). After placing an order, you will receive an email from us acknowledging that we have received your order. It will state what the item(s) you have ordered are, the cost (including VAT and postage and packaging) and delivery, invoice and cancellation details. If your order has been unsuccessful, you will be made aware of the reason why and possible explanations. Please note that this acknowledgment email does not mean that your order has been accepted – your order constitutes an offer to us to purchase goods or services. All orders are subject to acceptance by us and we will confirm such acceptance by sending you an email confirming that we have dispatched the item(s) to you (the Dispatch Confirmation). That email shall represent our legal acceptance of the offer you made to purchase the item(s) and the contract between us (the Contract) will only be formed (and we will debit your account) when we send you the Dispatch Confirmation. 

If we confirm to you that some but not other item(s) that you have ordered have been dispatched, those item(s) that have not been dispatched will not form part of the Contract. In the event of any change, such as a change in price or expected delivery date between completion of your order and Contract formation, we shall inform you and you shall at that point have the right to either (i) accept such change (in which case your email reply will represent a new offer which we will accept upon notification of dispatch) or (ii) reject such change (in which case your email reply will represent a withdrawal of your order, or the relevant part of your order as the case may be). If you have already paid for the item(s), we will refund the full amount no later than 30 days after the date of your order. 

Back to top

The goods will be at your risk and responsibility from the time we despatch your parcel for delivery. 

Ownership of the goods will pass to you when we receive full payment of all sums due in respect of the goods, including delivery charges. 

Back to top

BBC Worldwide aims to ensure that the pricing of goods and services on BBC Shop is correct at all times. However, the web pages may not always accurately reflect the correct details at the moment at which you place your order. BBC Worldwide reserves the right to change prices without prior notice at any time prior to dispatch. BBC Worldwide cannot confirm the price of an item until your order is accepted via the Dispatch Confirmation. For information on Pre-Orders, please [**click here.**](https://www.bbcshop.com/scat/ordering#preordering)

All prices include VAT (at the UK rate) where applicable, but exclude delivery costs, which will be added to the total amount. If the rate of VAT changes between the date of your order and the date of delivery, we will adjust the VAT you pay, unless you have already paid for the products in full before the change in VAT takes effect. 

Goods dispatched by BBC Shop to addresses outside of the European Union are generally not subject to VAT. 

All credit and charge card holders are subject to validation checks and authorisation by the card issuer. If the issuer of your payment card refuses to authorise payment to us, your order will not be accepted and BBCW will not be liable for any delay or non-delivery. For information on Payment options [**click here.**](https://www.bbcshop.com/scat/usefulinfo#paymentinformation)

Back to top

At the BBC Shop we want to provide you with the best possible customer service. We hope you are delighted with your items. However:   

    * If your order is faulty, damaged or mis-described, return it to us within 30 days of delivery for a full refund (including delivery charges); 
    * If you change your mind:   
o Return your item and write to us at bbcshop@bbc.com within 7 working days of delivery to cancel your order, and your consumer rights entitle you to a full refund (including delivery charges);  
o Return your item within 30 days of delivery, and provided it’s in an unused and saleable condition, we will refund the cost of the item (but not the delivery charges).(Certain items are excluded, however, please see the list below).

If you need to return your goods please follow our Returns and Refunds Procedure.

**Returns and Refunds Procedure**

a. Certain items are excluded from refunds or exchanges unless they are faulty. We cannot accept order cancellations or offer a refund or exchange on:

    * Personalised products  

    * Unsealed CDs, DVDs, tapes or other recording media, software or video.  
b. For all other items, please complete the Returns Form on the reverse of your despatch note.  
c. It’s important that your returns are in the best possible condition, so please ensure you wrap the item you’re returning securely, remembering to enclose the Returns Form.  
d. You must obtain a proof of delivery receipt from the Post Office Counter. This is your proof of return and must be provided if the item you are returning fails to arrive at our Returns Warehouse.  
e. Please allow 14 working days for the goods to be returned and for us to process your return.  
f. The product must be received by our Returns Department within 30 days of receipt of delivery.  
g. If the item is faulty, misdescribed or delivered in error, you will be fully refunded, including all postage costs.  
h. No claims can be processed unless these conditions are strictly adhered to.

All returns should be sent to:

BBC Shop  
Returns Department  
Technicolour Unit A  
Cosford Lane  
Newbold   
Rugby CV21 1QN  
England

This BBC Shop refund policy is separate and additional to your right to cancel under the Distance Selling Regulations. It does not affect your legal rights relating to faulty or mis-described goods. Contact your local Consumer Rights organisation (such as the Citizens Advice Bureau) if you would like more information on your legal rights.

Back to top

All rights, including copyright, in the content of the BBC Shop web pages are owned, licensed to or controlled for these purposes by BBCW. In accessing BBCW's web pages, you agree that you may only download the content for your own individual and non-commercial use. You are not permitted to copy, broadcast, download, store (in any medium), transmit, show or play in public, adapt or change in any way the content of these BBC Shop web pages for any other purpose whatsoever without the prior written permission of BBCWW. 

Back to top

### 11\. Force majeure (Events outside of our control)

BBCW shall have no liability to you for any failure to deliver goods you have ordered or any delay in doing so or for any damage or defect to goods delivered that is caused by any event or circumstance beyond its reasonable control. We will contact you as soon as reasonably possible in such an event. 

Back to top

If we fail to comply with these Terms, we are responsible for loss or damage you suffer that is a foreseeable result of our breach of these Terms or our negligence, but we are not responsible for any loss which is not foreseeable. Loss or damage is foreseeable if it was an obvious consequence of our breach or if it was contemplated by you and us at the time we entered into the contract. 

We only supply the items for domestic and private use. You agree not to use the items for business, commercial or re-sale purposes and we have no liability to you for loss of profit, loss of business, business interruption or loss of business opportunity. 

Nothing in these terms and conditions shall exclude or limit BBCW’s liability for: 

• death or personal injury as a result of BBCW’s negligence;  
• BBCW’s fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;   
• any breach of the terms implied by section 12 of the Sale of Goods Act 1979;  
• any breach of the terms implied by sections 13 to 15 of the Sale of Goods Act 1979;   
• defective products under the Consumer Protection Act 1987 

Back to top

### 13\. Safe Shopping - secure guarantee 

BBCW places great importance on maintaining the security of the information that you provide and for this reason we use advanced Internet security system to safeguard your data. In addition, we are GeoTrust approved and have a GeoTrust True Business ID Certificate. All the data that you send through, including your credit/debit card number and name and address, is encrypted and converted into code before it is transmitted across the Internet. Therefore in the extremely unlikely event that the data should be intercepted, it would be encrypted and difficult to decipher. 

Back to top

We take your privacy very seriously and are registered under the Data Protection Act. BBCW collects and processes data in accordance with our [**Privacy Policy**](https://www.bbcshop.com/scat/securityandprivacy#privacypolicy). Please take the time to read this Privacy Policy as it contains terms which apply to you. By using BBC Shop you consent to such collection and processing and you warrant that all data provided by you is accurate.

Back to top

### 15\. Transfer of Rights and Obligations

The contract between you and BBCW is binding on you and us and on our respective successors and assigns. You may not transfer, assign, charge or otherwise dispose of a Contract, or any of your rights or obligations arising under it, without our prior written consent. We may transfer, assign, charge, sub-contract or otherwise dispose of a Contract, or any of our rights or obligations arising under it, at any time during the term of the Contract.

Back to top

If we fail, at any time during the term of a Contract, to insist upon strict performance of any of your obligations under the Contract or any of these terms and conditions, or if we fail to exercise any of the rights or remedies to which we are entitled under the Contract, this shall not constitute a waiver of such rights or remedies and shall not relieve you from compliance with such obligations. A waiver by us of any default shall not constitute a waiver of any subsequent default.

Back to top

These terms and conditions and any document expressly referred to in them represent the entire agreement between us in relation to the subject matter of any Contract and supersede any prior agreement, understanding or arrangement between us, whether oral or in writing.

We each acknowledge that, in entering into a Contract, neither of us has relied on any representation, undertaking or promise given by the other or be implied from anything said or written in negotiations between us prior to such Contract except as expressly stated in these terms and conditions.

Neither of us shall have any remedy in respect of any untrue statement made by the other, whether orally or in writing, prior to the date of any Contract (unless such untrue statement was made fraudulently) and the other party´s only remedy shall be for breach of contract as provided in these terms and conditions. 

Back to top

### 18\. Invalidity and Governing Law & Jurisdiction

If for any reason part of these terms and conditions is unenforceable, the validity of the remaining terms and conditions shall not be affected.

Contracts between you and BBCW shall be governed by English law and you and BBCW submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales.

Back to top

## Verified by Visa and Mastercard SecureCode 

### 1\. Visa and Mastercard SecureCode 

Verified by Visa and Mastercard SecureCode are new services that protect your card details with a personal password in order to provide greater security to online shoppers. 

In order for Verified by Visa and Mastercard Secure Code to work, you will need to register your card with a password (which will be known only by you). You only need to do this once, then whenever you use the card to shop online, you will be asked to enter the password during the checkout process. 

If you are not already registered for Verified by Visa or Mastercard Secure Code, you may be asked by your bank to register your card during the BBC Shop online checkout process and you will be directed to your bank's website to do so. If you would like to register your card without placing an order online at BBC Shop, you will need to contact the bank that issued your credit card. 

If you have previously registered for Verified by Visa or Mastercard Secure Code, you will be prompted to enter your password when placing your order online at BBC Shop. 

For further information regarding these services visit: 

**Verified by Visa click[h ere](http://www.visae%20%20urope.com/personal/o%20%20nlineshopping/main.js%20%20p)**.

**Mastercard Secure please click[h ere](http://www.mast%20%20ercard.com/securecd/w%20%20elcome.do)**. 

Back to top

## EU Delivery Terms and Conditions

### 1\. Introduction to EU Delivery Terms and Conditions

Delivery to an EU Member State (other than the UK) of any goods purchased from BBC Worldwide Limited on www.bbcshop.com (“BBC Shop”) is provided to you by Technicolor Video Services Ltd (“TECHNICOLOR”, “We” or “Us”). BBC Worldwide Limited (“BBCW”) sell, but do not deliver, goods to customers located in EU Member States (other than the UK). This page sets out the terms and conditions on which delivery of such goods is provided by Technicolor. Please read these terms and conditions carefully before ordering any goods from the BBC shop and confirming your delivery option. By choosing to accept delivery of your goods to an EU Member State (other than the UK), you are contracting with Technicolor and you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions. These terms and conditions are subject to change at any time, and it is your responsibility to check these terms and conditions regularly before ordering any goods in case there are any changes. 

Back to top

Once BBCW accepts your order to purchase goods, BBCW shall confirm such acceptance by sending you an email confirming that Technicolor has dispatched the goods(s) to you (the “Dispatch Confirmation”). The contract between you and BBCW for the purchase of the goods, and also the contract between you and TECHNICOLOR for the delivery of the goods, takes effect when BBCW sends you the Dispatch Confirmation. 

You will be charged for the delivery service when the order you submit on the BBC Shop is accepted by BBCW. Upon receipt of your order, BBCW will collect your payment for the delivery service by Technicolor on behalf of Technicolor.

Back to top

### 3\. Availability and Delivery

Information regarding delivery times is clearly displayed on the BBC Shop next to the goods. If no delivery date is specified, your order will be fulfilled within 30 days of the date of the Dispatch Confirmation, unless there are exceptional circumstances. 

When We deliver the goods, you (or the recipient of the goods if different), may be required to sign on receipt of delivery. This signature will be used as proof that we have delivered the goods.

All goods will be delivered to the address that you indicate when you complete the ‘delivery’ page of the BBC Shop. We currently deliver to the countries listed at [insert link to page]. 

Back to top

The goods will be at your risk from the time of delivery.   
Ownership of the goods will only pass to you when BBCW receives full payment of all sums due in respect of the goods, including delivery charges. 

Back to top

All delivery charges shown on the BBC shop are inclusive of any taxes where applicable.   
If you order goods for delivery outside the UK, they may be subject to import duties and taxes which are levied when the delivery reaches the specified destination. You will be responsible for payment of any such import duties and taxes. Please note that we have no control over these charges and cannot predict their amount. Please contact your local customs office for further information before placing your order.

Please also note that you must comply with all applicable laws and regulations of the country for which the goods are destined. We are not liable for any breach by you of any such laws.

Back to top

### 6\. Data Protection and Privacy Policy

In order to provide you with a delivery service, we will need to provide your personal information to our delivery partners so that they can arrange with you the delivery of the goods.

We will process your personal information, and provide it to our delivery partners, in accordance with our privacy policy which is incorporated into these terms and conditions, a copy of which can be found here [insert link to TECHNICOLOR privacy policy]

Back to top

or
